[{"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You got me the air conditioner", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "My buddy works in an appliance store and he got us thirty percent off", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Good one? It's the Commando 8", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Okay, so, I'm gonna measure the window up, okay buddy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah.", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You just gotta mention my name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "That's it. ", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, in a second, in a second.  What do you mean you can't tell me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm asking", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, we just got those in. It's a very exciting new frame", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "All right, you have a prescription", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Not shot, dog bite", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Okay? That's it? I don't need a shot", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, no, no. I know I wasn't shot. Do I need a shot", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Not shot, dog bite", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Not shot, dog bite. Woof woof, not bang bang. ", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, you remember yesterday? Beautiful day... good day to be... out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh you must have done something", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, nothing really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well, I did go out for a little while", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Saw me? With who", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Saw me? With who", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "There's nothing to tell", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I knew there had to be another side to you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "There is a side, an ugly side", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No, no, there's no side", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, no, no ugly side", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Ooh, everything was going so well. She hadn't seen any flaws in me. Now she sees a side", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "A bad side, an ugly side", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well he frightened me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No. He said I didn't need a shot", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Did you get the shot", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You got bit by a strange dog and you didn't get a rabies shot", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "That's right, no discount", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yes, I mentioned your name", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What is going on here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'm talking about the thirty percent discount", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Oh he'll be home, it's Friday night. That's the big night on the Nature Channel", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "He does look like a horse", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "And I'd like a discount", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Listen, you're lucking I'm not asking for a refund. You gave me ladies' frames", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Come on in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Glasses.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Hello my friend", "qsentId": 46}]